https://www.pmrsinc.com/legal-terms/

HomeServicesManufacturing ServicesManufacturing EquipmentHot Melt ExtrusionProcess Analytical Technology (PAT)API Bioavailability EnhancementAnalytical ServicesMethod Development and ValidationRaw MaterialsRelease TestingChemical Analysis Equipment ListICP-MS TestingQuality ServicesOur Quality AssuranceIT ServicesMicrobiological ServicesFacilityVirtual TourThe Analytical LabOn the Path to Real Time ReleasePurified Water SystemOnline Water Bioburden AnalyzerRFID TrackingComplianceInspectionsEnvironmental ComplianceAbout UsOur PeopleCore ValuesThe PMRS AdvantageEnvironmental CommitmentContact UsCareers
HomeServicesManufacturing ServicesManufacturing EquipmentHot Melt ExtrusionProcess Analytical Technology (PAT)API Bioavailability EnhancementAnalytical ServicesMethod Development and ValidationRaw MaterialsRelease TestingChemical Analysis Equipment ListICP-MS TestingQuality ServicesOur Quality AssuranceIT ServicesMicrobiological ServicesFacilityVirtual TourThe Analytical LabOn the Path to Real Time ReleasePurified Water SystemOnline Water Bioburden AnalyzerRFID TrackingComplianceInspectionsEnvironmental ComplianceAbout UsOur PeopleCore ValuesThe PMRS AdvantageEnvironmental CommitmentContact UsCareers Legal Terms
PMRS LEGAL AND PRIVACY INFORMATIONCopyright © 2019 PMRS, Inc. All rights reserved.Terms and Conditions of UseWelcome to the corporate site of PMRS, Inc. (“PMRS”). Use for this site is governed by the Terms and Conditions set forth. PLEASE READ THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THE PMRS WEB SITE. The information and materials provided by PMRS may be used for informational purposes only.RestrictionsYou may view, download and copy information and materials available on this Web site solely for your personal, non-commercial use. As a condition of use, you agree not to modify or revise any of the material in any manner, and to retain all copyright and other proprietary notices as contained in the original materials on any copies of the materials. No other use of the materials or information is authorized. Any violation of the foregoing may result in civil and/or criminal liabilities.Privacy PolicyPMRS respects your right to online privacy including the protection of any personal information (PI) you share with us. We define personal information as any information that can be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, first and last name, a home or business address, email addresses or phone number(s).If you provide us with your personal information, PMRS may transfer that information within PMRS or partners who are authorized to act on PMRS’s behalf. We take steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect personal information on PMRS’s behalf.PMRS intends to take all reasonable and appropriate steps to protect your information from unauthorized access and disclosure. You may choose whether or not to provide personal information to PMRS.TrackingPMRS has the ability to utilize tracking tools that record information such as Internet domain, host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, and dates and times when our Web site is accessed. We may use such information to improve our site, prevent fraud or troubleshoot.LinksOur web sites may contain links to other sites. PMRS is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personal information.Changes to the Terms and Conditions or Privacy PolicyThe Internet is an evolving medium. PMRS may at any time revise and update the Terms and Conditions or Privacy Policy. You are encouraged to periodically visit this page to review the most current versions to which you are bound. If you do not agree to these Terms and Conditions of Use, or Privacy Policy, please do not use this Web site.Any future changes our privacy policy, will get posted on this page before they take effect. That posting will be the only notice given of any such changes.Your ConsentBy using, accessing or downloading materials from this Web site, you agree to follow the terms and provisions as outlined in this legal notice, which apply to all visits to the PMRS Web site, both now and in the future.CAN-SPAM NoticeThis website does not give, sell, or otherwise transfer any information including email addresses for the use in bulk communications such as bulk emails. Such use of any such information obtained at this website, any related website, or any website pointing to this notice is illegal and/or strictly prohibited.For more information about the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 and its requirements for businesses, please refer to http://business.ftc.gov/documents/bus61-can-spam-act-compliance-guide-business/.©  2020 PMRS, Inc. All Rights Reserved. Legal Terms
